[Music]
hey
hey hey
[Music]
heyy well good morning everyone and
welcome to the Fiverr Broadband
Association five for breakfast we're now
in our seventh episode of 2025 before we
kick off I'd like to thank Wesco the
Platinum sponsor for five for breakfast
yesterday was the fiber Broadband
association's first Regional fiber
connect Workshop in San Antonio for 2025
we had record attendance as Texas will
be by far the largest recipient of bead
infrastructure funding with 3.3
billion as of June last summer uh we
estimated that about nearly 6% % of the
homes in Texas are either unserved or
underserved and during yesterday's fiber
connnect Workshop we heard from the
Federal Reserve on the economic outlook
for Texas from the governor's Broadband
Development Council and the Texas
Broadband development office there also
sessions on permitting and case studies
and how underserved communities in Texas
have got fiber um it just amazing lineup
of speakers and highly relevant topics
today um the fber Broadband
association's policy committee is in
auson Texas where we're meeting with the
state legislature we look forward to
some very productive discussions and how
we can work together to ensure that we
can deliver fiber to every Home and
Community in the state our next fiber
connect Workshop is coming up on March
25th in Philadelphia the city City of
Brotherly Love and then we be um our
fiber day on the hill um this year is in
April then we'll have our big annual
conference fiber connect 2025 in
National
June 1st to 4th that is going to be
absolutely amazing with over 5,000
people we'll be in Anchorage in July
Toronto and August smokane in September
Scottdale in October Kansas City in
November and then we'll have our Premier
member meeting in Palm Springs December
8th and 9th and that brings us today's
fire for breakfast with former FCC
chairman a Jeep Pi partner at search
light Capital he'll be discussing
Broadband priorities in the new
Administration expanding access speed
and
Equity before I finally in US Today's
guest I'd like to introduce David Norris
from our team who's going to walk us
through some housekeeping
items thank you very much Gary and thank
you for joining us this morning uh we
appreciate it before I go over few
legistics we'd like to once again thank
our Platinum sponsor fiber for breakfast
Westco now please keep in mind all
participants are in listen only mode
today however if you have a question
please type it into the question box
located within the control panel on the
side of your screen and we will get to
those questions when we host the Q&A
session with our panelists at the end of
today's presentation this presentation
is also being recorded and will be
available on fba's website within 24 to
48 hours and you can find that recording
in the events tab under the fiber for
practice dropdown option finally at the
conclusion of today's presentation
you'll be prompted to complete a brief
feedback survey we appreciate your input
so if you could take a moment to do so
that would be great with that I will
hand things back over to Gary to get us
started Gary thanks David and good
morning I'm Gary Bolton the president
CEO of the fiber Broadband Association
you know last week on fire for breakfast
Our Guest was Peter sepino Wall Street
senior analyst and managing director for
Wolf research who discussed the
Broadband Market Outlook key trends you
know Peter walked us through his
thoughts and predictions on broadband
subscriber growth and saturation and why
isp's win where they have fivr and his
views on the market on Market
consolidation in the coming years if you
missed last week's session you can go to
our website and watch the replay today
in fire for breakfast Our Guest is
former FCC chairman a Jeep Pi partner at
search like Capital who's going to be
discussing Broadband priorities in the
new Administration expanding access
speed and Equity prior to joining
joining search light in 2021 a was the
chairman of the FCC which he led from
2017 to 2021 during his tenure as
chairman he implemented major
initiatives to help close the digital
divide Advanced us leadership in 5G open
ran Wi-Fi 6 and other Wireless
Technologies promote Innovation protect
consumers Public Safety and National
Security and make the agency itself more
open transparent and data driven uh Mr
Pi first joined the FCC as commercial
commissioner in 2012 before becoming a
commissioner he served in various
positions in increasing responsibilities
at the FCC US Department of Justice the
US Senate and previously he was a
partner at Jenner and block and served
as in-house council at Verizon Mr Pi
serves on very portfolio company boards
and he received his AB with uh is that
AB or ba with honors from Harvard
University and a JD from the University
of Chicago Law School so welcome
chairman pi and for audience please type
in your questions as we go and work them
into our discussion with that let's get
things kicked off so let's start with uh
Your Role um leading the FCC during the
last Trump Administration What would you
say were your greatest
achievements uh well first Gary thanks
so much to you and the the fiber bar
association for inviting me to
participate it's h been a pleasure
working with you over the years and
culminating this conversation today it's
it's a nice Capstone to our joint
efforts in these Vineyards uh working at
the FCC was a tremendous honor we were
sprinting from day one until our last
day and got a lot across the finish line
that I'm really proud of but I suppose
the thing that I'm most proud of is the
work we took to help close the digital
divide to massively increase the in
incentive to uh invest in highquality
infrastructure and fiber Broadband
infrastructure in particular if you look
at my various statements and speeches
over the years you'll see peppered into
them on occasion references to the fiber
Broadband association's reports
detailing how much fiber was being
deployed that we were consistently
setting records in 2019 2020 2021 and to
me that was a good marker of the efforts
that we were taking to ensure that every
American has access access not just to
broadband but to best-in-class broadband
so that by the end of our time and
certainly going forward Our Hope was
that no American would be left in a
relative slow lane compared to some of
their more urban brethren in particular
so I'm really proud of the initiatives
that we took to help close that digital
divide small and large the other things
you mentioned 5G Wi-Fi uh making the
agency more transparent and National
Security and Public Safety it's hard to
pick among your children so to speak but
really that closing that digital divide
was so important especially since at the
end of my tenure we went directly into
the covid pandemic when Broadband
networks really stood the test uh and
nobody was sure going into it that they
would and so to me it was Vindication
that we had our eye on the right
prize yeah and actually you know
building out the critical fiber
infrastructure uh really kind of
leverages um you know U National
Security um Wireless infrastructure 5G
you know and also so um you know Wi-Fi
and so forth so it's all kind of Builds
on the fiber as the foundation so we
really you know appreciate your
leadership uh during your long tenure
the FCC and as and your leadership at
the FCC um so you know as you were
leaving you know that was a challenge
because you had to get Ard off out
really quick um as the days were ticking
down to um you know the next
Administration um given what you know
now what what might have you done
different with Ard off
it's a good question so I think uh
several points number one had we known
that there would be a number of public
Vehicles Public Funding vehicles coming
behind it including the $42 billion for
bead the capital projects fund and other
legislative Vehicles like that we
obviously would have structured it
differently our thought was that this
was the only certain funding stream that
we could think of and so uh we had to
structure that over the decade to come a
10-year program of course and the second
thing is just the political reality
ities uh you know I knew from the outset
uh because they told me that two of my
colleagues were going to be automatic
NOS on whatever I proposed so you know I
had to get three votes and you just
reality of negotiation was that I had to
broaden the program beyond what I wanted
to focus it on and so that ultimately
ended up in the program that was
structured as it was and so we obviously
opened it up to basically any technology
U and we also had to structure the
program in such a way to incentivize uh
or at least allow participation from
those who might be looking to build
beyond their traditional Footprints or
even States and so you we obviously
would have structured things differently
encouraged more and these are things
that I now uh advocate for when I talk
to State Broadband directors or nia or
anybody else with Broadband equities in
the policy space is to ensure you know
accountability both on the back end but
also on the front end are these credible
operators that you believe will be
responsible stewards of the public Fisk
once they were handed the these monies
and so that's one of the things that for
the companies that we back now at
searchlight I personally have worked
very extensively with some of these
companies that nobody will necessarily
know the name of on the national stage
but nonetheless these are the fiber
providers who are really focused on
closing that digital divide they're the
foot soldiers of the Broadband
revolution in a lot of these rural areas
and so those are the types of folks that
we really want to encourage to
participate in you know artof back then
bead now and any other programs like
them well you you have a a a very unique
perspective because you've served as a
regulator um and now you're in the
private sector so as a partner at search
light um how does your firm view fiber
from an investment
perspective we are very bullish on fiber
at the beginning of my tenure at search
light back in 2021 we did a very deep
dive uh we are not a an investment firm
that you know sees the hot shiny new
object out there and seizes it we really
do what we call thematic investing where
before allocating capital from that is
given to us by our LPS we really sit
down and think okay what is our thesis
around this particular uh theme in the
sector and when it comes to Telecom we
studied all the Technologies all the
different markets and what we thought
was that the one consistent theme in the
consumer Broadband experience since the
dawn of the commercial internet in the
1990s is that they're always consuming
more bandwidth and that applications and
services are going to scale accordingly
to consume more bandwidth moreover what
we thought was that there were starting
to emerge at the time and certainly we
see it now too uh the need for more
symmetric capabilities things like tella
health or gaming or even just doing high
quality video calls and things like that
that was going to require uh more
symmetric capabilities and especially as
fiber penetrated as Broadband penetrated
more into rural areas you can see things
like Precision agriculture requiring
very high capacity upload not just
download and so to us at least as we
thought thought about the technologies
that were capable of doing that fiber
seemed to be the best technology and
moreover we saw from some of our
portfolio companies that were
overbuilding themselves with fiber and
here I'm thinking of zipley in the
Pacific Northwest and Consolidated which
is in a number of states but
predominantly the Northeast in those
areas where we had copper infrastructure
that we inherited and were overbuilding
it with fiber we saw tremendous consum
response the penetration rates that we
had underwritten for example were
exceeded far in front of the benchmarks
and I think that indicated that there's
something here that consumers really
like about fiber and the gigabit product
in particular even if they might not
consume a gigabit or necessarily know
all of the things that a gigabit
connection could enable them to do it's
something they found very attractive
because it gave them the sense of
reliability capacity and obviously we
encourage our companies to do it at a
price point that's competitive with some
of the others in the market and so all
of which is to say at search like we are
believers uh in fiber in particular
markets and we're now doing that in
rural areas as I mentioned we have
companies in Virginia Arizona and
Indiana where I helped work spearhead
some of those Investments and these are
uh companies that are just really doing
some exciting things in small towns and
I I guess you might say excerpts in some
cases building fiber and making the
business cases work thanks in part to
our Equity capital and other financial
instruments we're able to raise for them
and it's super exciting uh to see the
look on the faces of some of our
customers our company's customers and
I've met some of them when they get a
fiber connection it's almost the sense
of we've arrived you know we're no
longer in this subordinated slow lane
when it comes to the digital economy and
you obviously we are looking to do well
through these Investments but more
importantly we're looking to do good and
we do feel like Fiverr enables us to say
we've done both Yeah you mentioned
zipley so as a regulator um you know we
saw the crtc um unbundle fiber in Canada
that that was that one of the um you
know kind of encouraged B Canada start
looking across the border to see you
know some investments in the US or what
what's your thought on
that yeah I'm not the Canadian
regulatory landscape is obviously
different you mentioned one of the key
points of difference uh I think for us
and you obviously Bell Canada should
speak for itself but I think what we
found was that we had created in zipley
a really attractive uh asset in that we
had best-in-class infrastructure we knew
how to compete and we were offering
these services at a price point that was
really attractive and gave us trem gave
the new buyer tremendous opportunities
uh to for growth and zipley now is still
in the process of finishing the
overbuild of itself it's looking to
expand in other parts of Oregon
Washington Idaho Montana and I think
that what maybe what B Canada saw is
what we saw is that there's a tremendous
opportunity for growth in some of these
markets in the Northwest where you you
have people who are willing to sign up
for and pay for high quality Broadband
uh they are looking for an alternative
in some cases where the incumbent might
not be as agile as they would like and
it's almost like the Field of Dreams if
you build it they will come and so to
build it of course requires a
substantial infusion uh of capital and
that's something that Bell Canada
certainly brings to the table and I
think also the US market having more
generally speaking of course uh every
Mark every state is different but
generally having a more deregulatory
approach is something that allowed Bell
Canada to pencil out return on invested
Capital that would be relatively
attractive to them so you know one of
the things that um you know with the um
U I guess policy makers they like to use
speed as a proxy for Broadband right and
during the the you know connected
America Funds you know we were at um you
know was 41 and 101 and 253 you know we
had all these different speeds which
encouraged um Regional providers to um
invest in DSL technology which then
resulted in uh them their market failure
and that had to restructure and now we
saw that now we see them investing in
fiber and becoming very very creative
like Frontier now with their merger with
a Verizon and so forth is can you now
now we have the you know kind of the um
advantage of being able to look back in
time is it a mistake to use speed as a
proxy versus you know when we see like R
Us and others have really looked at this
investment more as critical
infrastructure rather than just you know
how do we give someone minimum
speeds yeah it's it's that's a great
question and it is funny now having
spent four years in the private sector I
sometimes smile looking back at some of
the fiercely debated topics at the FCC
during my tenure one of which of course
was speed thresholds and I'm old enough
to remember when it was was a 268 uh
kils way back 20 years ago and uh it
then increasing it to 25 over three
should be 100 over 20 should be
gigabit not to me a lot of that is just
noise from now what I can say with some
confidence is that I think that policy
makers should view it from the consumer
perspective where is the consumer now
and where is the consumer going to be in
five years 10 years 25 years and this is
something I did say when I was at the
FCC to my partial credit um but so I
think in a sense it doesn't really
matter what the speed threshold is as is
pronounced by a particular majority the
FCC in Washington or by a lawmaker what
really matters is where the Puck is
going from a consumer perspective and
that's part of the reason why we are so
bullish at search light at least on
fiber because fiber now you have all of
these trends that are serving as
Tailwinds one is of course the consumer
expectation which we've discussed
another one is the rise of an entire
pocket of private Capital infrastructure
Capital that has a lower rate of return
expectation also a much longer time
Horizon these aren't you know three to
five year private Equity Investments
these are more 7even to 10 years and
Beyond Investments so very relatively
longer term investments uh that that
people are looking for and on top of
that you have a sense that this is
enduring infrastructure that reduces
substantially the cost that's involved
on an Opex P from an Opex perspective
you don't have to have a lot of truck
roles you can have visibility directly
into the network a lot easier than you
would would say a DSL Network or even an
hfc Network things like that and so I
think that people have come around to
viewing this as sort of core
infrastructure which is not how they
viewed Broadband at all I'd say from a
from a p perspective at least 10 20
years ago and so all of those things are
combining I think and you're seeing that
now you mentioned some of the deals
Verizon Frontier of course zipley Bell
Canada people are recognizing that
there's something about fiber that gives
it a very longlived infrastructure uh
Lifetime and that's something that's
very attractive not just from an
investment perspective but importantly
from a consumer perspective this is
infrastructure that consumers know I
won't say future proof because like you
know nothing is future proof if we've
learned anything we know that technology
is always racing ahead but I do think is
an EXT extremely long-lived asset that
is somewhat akin to the railroads of the
19th century and certainly the telephone
networks of the 20th century this is
infrastructure that people want and
expect to be there when they need it and
that's part of the reason why we think
there are a lot of very good secular
Tailwinds for Fiber Well absolutely I
mean you know twisted pair and you know
we had five NES of reliability for the
old pstn and then when data overtook
voice is the you know really the main
application now fibers the critical
infrastructure for the next Century um
so can you what can you tell us about
your role on the Trump transition team
and kind of um and more do you see
things
going yeah well I can't say a lot it's
sort of like Fight Club I suppose right
I can't the first rule is not to
disclose too much but what I will say is
that the Trump campaign the transition
team and now of course the
administration is singularly focused on
making sure that we have the framework
in place from a policy perspective to
build things in America get rid getting
rid of some of the regulatory obstacles
that are out there making sure that
people have the maximum incentive to
raise and invest Capital making sure
that work crews are put get put back to
work uh building these high quality
networks across the country and to the
extent that my advice was solicited
that's the number one thing I encourage
them to think about is yeah how do we
make sure that our goal of making
getting every American connected who
wants a high quality connection can
happen it just Broadband doesn't fall
from trees as know better than anybody
and so that's what the campaign what the
transition team and the administration I
think are going to be focused on is yeah
let's get rid of some of the rules in
Washington that are standing in the way
of work Crews putting fiber and other
highquality Technologies into the ground
and into the air in some
cases yeah no I was really excited I
thought that John um stany of AT&T did a
great job after the election to you know
demonstrate where they thought the right
investment was for them and getting you
know targeted $50 million homes by the
end of 2029 and you know how it Advanced
their business case and um you know how
it's able to attach their Wireless and
other um you know reduce their op so and
create jobs um you know so one of the
things I'm I'm confused about you know
and you know we're really excited about
the new Administration we're really
excited about you know really the focus
on getting things deployed make things
happen faster lighter regulatory
environment all the good things that are
going to come with this new
Administration uh but during you know
Howard lck's um Senate hearings you know
there's a lot of concern that was voiced
um was about um you know niti's priority
on fiber especially when it comes to
extremely high costs um as an investor
you know you guys see fiber is very ACC
creative and you know why there there
seem to be a gap between the private
sector and what the private sector is
willing to spend their money on and what
policy makers think's a good investment
for
taxpayers yeah and we'll get to that in
a second but I do want to piggyback off
something you said about John stank's
remarks which I think were spoton but it
was also critically paired with uh
AT&T's announcement that they really
want to start retiring some of this
aging infrastructure that's in place and
they hope that the new FCC led by
Brennan Carr of course as the new
chairman will help them do that and I
think those two things are such
important halves of the of the coin and
I was screaming this from the rooftops
when I was a commissioner back in 2012
2013 every dollar that is invested in
Copper by definition cannot be invested
in fiber and so to the extent that we
can allow companies like ad& anybody
else in this space with aging
infrastructure to refocus its
Investments to you know get Capital
allocation looking to the Future as
opposed to maintaining the past that's a
good thing not just for those companies
not just for the industry but for the
American Consumer so you spot on your
point that you made about that I mean
thanks for bringing that up because you
know the CEOs of um isps across our
membership saying every dollar they have
to spend on copper is a dollar not being
spent on fiber and why are we doing that
right and I can tell you at search light
I have a foot in both camps you zipling
Consolidated of course with more have
inherited more copper based TDM networks
and so I see how difficult it is for
them in some of these cases but then on
the other side I see the opportunities
for some of our fiber only fiber first
companies like the ones I mentioned in
and for them they don't have to worry
about Legacy it systems and OSS BSS
transition and how you know how do you
deal with the customer service requests
uh you how do you m persuade them to
migrate from Cooperative all those
things just melt away when you're
starting with fiber so you the future is
out there if policy makers can catch up
to where the consumer and where these
companies want to go from a
technological perspective
but well even further is um I'm GNA have
the president Hawaiian ton in a couple
weeks and you know by their copper
retirement they really accelerated their
um zeroc carbon footprint um priorities
you know when you get rid of all the
Opex and all the you know your your the
carbon footprint that from a fiber a
copper Network you're able to really get
to a more sustainable uh Network so
anyway yeah let's get into um so why is
there a gap between you know what um the
private um investors are putting their
Capital end versus what policy makers
think is good for the you know Americans
or taxpayer investment yeah so I think
part of the Gap is due to bead's
implementation in this case and you've
heard this repeatedly uh not just from
you policy makers but just from average
people why was this money allocated $42
billion in 2021 and still not a single
household has been connected with
broadband and for all of the complaints
about Ard off at least you can say that
all closing in on one million customers
consumers consuming households I should
say have been connected with Broadband
today compared to when arof started you
relative to bead where you four years
later not a single shovel is hit the
ground and so I think there's a
frustration between the promise of bead
as was enunciated back in 2021 and the
reality of implementation in 2025 which
is that cumbersome processes and
regulatory requirements and whatever
other factors people might identify that
stood in the way of bead funding getting
out there and from a private perspective
as well you look we we actually believe
what we saw in the terms of the statute
and the notice of funding opportunity
that okay this is going to be the
timeline and so we organize our Capital
allocation activities accordingly and so
honestly was a surprise to us that at
the end of 2024 you still had states
that whose volume twos had not been
approved uh there's all sorts of
regulatory requirements that didn't seem
to be specified in the law that seem to
be uh you know being maintained in some
of these State volume 2's at the niti's
request Etc and so all which is to say
that I think that you saw hearing was a
little bit of a disjunction between that
has been created because of this Gap in
expectations I thought the secretary
designate did a masterful job
enunciating the basic point that
everybody not just people in our space
but everybody expects government should
get the benefit of the bargain and the
bargain was that we will allocate this
$42 billion in public spending and we
will do it in an efficient way that gets
consumers connected to broadband and I
obviously don't want to read too much
into what the questions were what the
answers were but I think that basic
principle is so important let's get rid
of some of the regulatory overhang that
stands in the way of these funds being
distributed make sure that we're be that
we as Americans are seeing these monies
being spent wisely and let's just get
people connected and that's something I
think that most people Republican and
Democrat would agree with uh it's
there's no Republican or Democrat when
it comes to getting Americans in these
rural areas unserved and underserved
areas connected with high quality Broad
well I mean we are just thrilled with
the speed of getting the secretary in
place and the assistant secretary in
place because you know um we got to
accelerate this program and we know that
newon Administration wants to accelerate
it so we want to minimize the review
period and you know to try to get the
revisions to streamline and accelerate
the whole program because you know these
Americans they're the ones that are um
you know kind of getting the short in
the stick right now and and also you
know we've had our member the supply
side have spent billions and billions to
move manufacturing the US have us jobs
and we can't allow us anything to stall
that's going to you know where they're
going to have to Furlow workers and you
know the factor is going to be quiet
waiting for you know the government to
figure out you know unwind what was done
and and try to redo the program so I'm
we're greatly appreciative of the
administration's efforts to be very
quick you know do the right thing but do
it as quickly as possible yeah and the
other thing to think about is that I
know we've been talking mainly about
residential Broadband new fiber in
particular but uh I think that one of
the things is really important is that
all of these things are interconnected
so for example all of the 5G and Next
Generation Wireless technology that's
being deployed will require uh fiber
connections for back haul all of these
massive data centers that are being
built across the country that are going
to require fiber connectivity you know
to to enable the transmission and
receipt of data all of that's going to
require fiber and so building out fiber
through beat or whatever program to
these residences is not simply limited
to connecting an individual consumer I
think it's a matter of just economic
growth and technological innovation yeah
fiber is almost like the Matrix if you
think about it it's it's everywhere it's
even here In This Very Room uh you you
can see it when you turn on your
television or you know when you pay your
tax that's sort of I don't want to over
state is pres ubiquity of course but all
which is to say that fiber in a sense is
backbone for all these different
Technologies and so I I think there's
been in some cases the false dichotomy
presented between fiber on one hand and
every other technology on the other hand
you know to me it's all part of a really
textured high quality Broadband Network
that just gets bits from point A to
point B in the most efficient way and I
hope is anyway that that's how policy
makers will see it going forward well
exactly I mean you know you get the
question of why would you spend 100,000
pulling fiber at a house that's only
worth 150,000 well
because you're building out the middle
mile infrastructure that allows you to
put more houses in there then it's going
to amortise that investment over more
houses and what we saw in Northeast
Louisiana is when Ven and Thomas were
able to get fiber to Northeast Louisiana
now meta is putting an AI DEA Center in
there and so you're creating all kinds
of Economic Development so you're not
just pulling fiber to one house but
you're really enabling the economic
growth of a rural you know low density
area to really be a you know just like
the way a railro would come to a town
and all a sudden you spur economic
activity in that community so hey um one
last question because I know that um you
know as an investor you have a really
good Insight on this but you know you
mentioned fiber is you know more about
more than just Broadband but what do you
what are the applications you're seeing
that really F
enables oh it's it's tremendous uh there
there are a lot of them so certainly AI
is the thing that we've been thinking
about a lot and we're looking at number
of companies in the AI space uh that are
leveraging high-capacity brandwidth in
order to very quickly and seamlessly you
connect a consumer to your particular
data center or other place where you
know that process that query can be
processed and delivered and so we're
looking a lot at some of the verticals
in the AI space uh and another one and
we haven't yet found uh you the killer
company the killer app but we're really
thinking a lot about tellah health tele
medicine some of those vertical which I
think are very exciting and it just
seems to fit the Need For You reducing
cost in the Health Care System the
closure of hospitals and other
Healthcare facilities particularly in
rural areas uh the advancement of
Technologies like 5G which I mentioned
and Wi-Fi and others that are going to
require fiber you know for to back all a
lot of that traffic so all of these
things are kind of pointing to I think
some really interesting breakthroughs in
tah health and so we're looking at that
as well I mentioned data centers where
we've become very focused uh and
Associated digital infrastructure like
Towers which I think uh are are going to
require High lot of fiber to be able to
connect with back hall and so you the
future is bright and that's part of the
reason why I say uh you know I think
that uh unfortunately in some Washington
debates there is a lot of oppositional
commentary about these Technologies and
you know I I see it as all part of a
really exciting time to innovate in the
United States and regardless of the
technology fixed wireless satellite
fiber let's let all of them compete
fairly and let the consumer and
essentially Drive business decisions you
through the aggregated wisdom that they
that they show us and you I'm confident
that if that happens you we'll we'll be
in a really strong position as a country
going
forward well chairman Pi I think I'm
gonna take the replay of this and listen
into it every morning when I get up to
get tot up the day because I'm so
excited about the future and thanks for
all your great leadership um at the FCC
um the transition with the new
Administration and as an investor in our
industry so thank you for everything you
do and I want to thank everybody for
joining us today um we're going to get
back together next Wednesday with Peter
CE is GNA talk about AI how AI
accelerates fiber Network value so um
you're not going to want to miss this
this is going to be a great talk so
again chairman Pi thanks again and we'll
look forward to seeing you soon thanks
so much appreciate
it all right hang on a minute if you
don't mind okay David were we good